(Sheldon:)Although advertised to appear,
he did not show up.
(Sheldon:)It was at that moment
I vowed eternal hatred for Wil Wheaton.
(Raj:)Okay, great,
you can tell him you hate him. Sign here.
It might interest you to know
that Wil Wheaton currently ranks sixth...
(Sheldon:)...on my all-time enemies list, right
between director Joel Schumacher...
(Sheldon:)...who nearly destroyed
the Batman movie franchise...
(Sheldon:)...and Billy Sparks,
who lived down the street from me...
(Sheldon:)...and put dog poop
on the handles of my bicycle.
(Raj:)Okay, I get it. He's a bad guy.
Sign here.
(Sheldon:)In the words of Khan Noonien Singh
in the immortal Wrath of Khan:
"He tasks me.
He tasks me and I shall have him."
(Raj:)-No doubt. Sign here.
-"From hell's heart, I stab at thee."
(Howard:)All right, Raj.
Looks like you're teamed up with...
..."Die, Wil Wheaton, die."
(Howard:)So tell me more
about the future mother of my children.